Thirty round clip and a wish
drop top and an all black whip
Got too many ms and it don't make sense
I cannot stand with a hole in my chest
Hopin’ I fall will a pint and the X
and my vision too blurry I speak for the tris
Getting me thru m*therf*cker I'm him
standing at the gates and I'm tryna get in
Said I'm tryna get in
aye, yuh b*tch I'm tryna get through
Knock on the door shoot a b*tch off a limb
where do I go to get help when I lose like
I might just overdose
blue, green, pink, on the bills like ducks
4 black walls in the room like ghosts
doing this till I die get a mic and a rope
I grip dat holster
bullets fly
Get up and stand in the line
feeling hopeless
What's the word
devlish when will I die
Is it done yet?
leavin’ this earth shoot a m*therf*cker pull out the .9
I'm in the hills
oxycotton crush it up and get high wasting my time
Wasting my time
crush it up and get high
Aye aye wasting my time
thirty round clip and a wish
Drop top and an all black whip
got too many ms and it don't make sense
I cannot stand with a hole in my chest
hopin’ I fall will a pint and the X
And my vision too blurry I speak for the tris
getting me thru m*therf*cker I'm him
Standing at the gates and I'm tryna get in
Thirty- thirty- thirty round clip and a wish
Drop top and an all black whip
got too many ms and it don't make sense
I cannot stand with a hole in my chest
hopin’ I fall will a pint and the X
And my vision too blurry I speak for the tris
getting me thru m*therf*cker I'm him
Standing at the gates and I'm tryna get in