That lil' b*tch she bad
I told her hold up
I cannot love no th*t
she playing like controller
All I want is f*cking bands
counting commas
Shout out Greedo
now I'm selling shows
At a five star casino
tell that b*tch to stop
Now drop
throw it back
If you talking sh*t I might
fold you like a Mac
That lil' b*tch a goth girl
yeah that's where it's at
You be under pressure no
it's not that's a fact
That lil' b*tch she bad
I told her hold up
I cannot love no th*t
she playing like controller
All I want is f*cking bands
counting commas
Shout out Greedo
now I'm selling shows
At a five star casino
tell that b*tch to stop
Now drop
throw it back
If you talking sh*t I might
fold you like a Mac
That lil' b*tch a goth girl
yeah that's where it's at
You be under pressure no
it's not thats a fact
Baby I be under pressure
with my homies
Smoking pressure
I can do this with no effort in
The backseat tearing leather
baby rubbing on my Ksubis
She just wanna feel the texture
my bro came an tried to warn
Me she might play me if I let her
but she sweet just like a Rolo
Go ahead stop and do it slow mo
yeah let's make this last forever
Baby go and take a photo
shorty got me taking risks
I feel like Drake I'm yelling YOLO
got me hypnotized the way
She bring it back jus like a yoyo
y'all be saying that they hard
But I be thinking that they so so
if you try and do me dirty
I'ma do you a Fabuloso
shoutout Rico that's
The bro bro
I cant switch yo that's
The bro code
that girl tryna play these games
But she a th*t on thats a no go
f*ck it one, two, come thru
Babygirl I want you
I been running through the city
But I'ma be home soon
three, four out the door skrrt off
Like Aventador
that lil' b*tch she bad
She got me going up in all the stores
five, six, seven, eight hit it like the renegade
We been waiting on this
for a minute time to celebrate
Now it's time for me to dash
sign off like the autograph
I might take her to the pad
wanna know why cause
That lil' b*tch she bad
I told her hold up
I cannot love no th*t
she playing like controller
All I want is f*cking bands
counting commas
Shout out Greedo
now I'm selling shows
At a five star casino
tell that b*tch to stop
Now drop
throw it back
If you talking sh*t I might
fold you like a Mac
That lil' b*tch a goth girl
yeah thats where it's at
You be under pressure no
it's not thats a fact
That lil' b*tch she bad
I told her hold up
I cannot love no th*t
she playing like controller
All I want is f*cking bands
counting commas
Shout out Greedo
now I'm selling shows
At a five star casino
tell that b*tch to stop
Now drop
throw it back
If you talking sh*t I might
fold you like a Mac
That lil' b*tch a goth girl
yeah thats where it's at
You be under pressure no
it's not thats a fact
The world is yours