If you think I'm pretty
lay your hands on me
Know you can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
I know that you're sh*tty
and you're bad for me
But I can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
If you think I'm pretty
lay your hands on me
Know you can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
I know that you're sh*tty
and you're bad for me
But I can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
Won't you give that sh*t
a rest?
Said you needed love
but you're only here for s*x, and
And I'm dyin'
to be next
Killed me
once before
I just come back
more obsessed with you
Nothin' that I need
to say
That hasn't been
said
I don't need
an apology
Just show me
you'd stay
If you think I'm pretty
lay your hands on me
Know you can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
I know that you're sh*tty
and you're bad for me
But I can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
(Won't stop
thinkin' 'bout it)
If you think I'm pretty
lay your hands on me
Know you can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
I know that you're sh*tty
and you're bad for me
But I can't stop
thinkin' 'bout it
If you think I'm pretty
pre-, pre-
Hands on, ha-ha-
know you-
If you-, if you-
pre-, pre-
If you think I'm pretty
Hands on, ha-ha-
know you-
If you think I'm pretty
lay your hands on me
hands on
(If you think I'm pretty
pre-pre-)
lay your hands on me)