As of lately haven't been myself
as of lately haven’t been myself
As of lately, ooh
oh, baby, haven't been myself
Ayy, ayy
off myself, let off a hunnid rounds
One moment, I'm gone, the memories lost
through like it’s lost and found
I can never go back and I cannot fathom
all of the thoughts around you
The bullets fly, you wanna die
I pull up, they surround you
Soul burning in hell like I cannot breathe
when it's dark outside and the lights go out
This choppa knock like guys
up at your front door, breathing ash and gun smoke
Getting up off my a*s, I'm breaking bread
like I done cut dough
But as of lately, I haven't fеlt myself
I stay inside the crib and I hold thе pain I felt
Like have you been good?
give me time, it's hard to tell
You a b*tch, you understood?
I got your b*tch, she do me well
As-as of lately, I haven't felt myself
I stay inside the crib and I hold the pain I felt
Like have you been good?
give me time, it's hard to tell
You a b*tch, you understood?
I got your b*tch, she do me well
As of lately haven't been myself
as of lately haven’t been myself
As of lately, ooh
oh, baby, haven’t been myself
Ever since you left, I haven't seen the sun
I’m always alone, I'm running for something I can't even see
My couch is always there for me
to feed the loneliness
I'm getting older
guess I gotta get with the new times
I get sick of the old rhymes
come in equipped with the .45
Baby, you got me so high, so high
so high, I can’t even breathe
My feet have left the ground
somebody save me from myself
Somebody come rescue me
baby bone so broken, I can only give you what's left of me
As of lately life is such a tragedy
yuh
As of lately, I haven't felt myself
I stay inside the crib and I hold the pain I felt
Like have you been good?
give me time, it's hard to tell
You a b*tch, you understood?
I got your b*tch, she do me well
As-as of lately, I haven't felt myself
I stay inside the crib and I hold the pain I felt
Like have you been good?
give me time, it's hard to tell
You a b*tch, you understood?
I got your b*tch, she do me well
As of lately haven't been myself
as of lately haven't been myself
As of lately, ooh
oh, baby, haven't been myself