How can someone feel like we did out there
have you lost the dream that was in our hands
Is it ok now
is it ok now
Find me
inside every heartbeat
Inside every worry
keep me in your heart again
Find me
inside every heartbeat (over the hills again)
Inside every worry
inside your heart
How can someone feel like we did out there
have you lost the dream that was in our hands
Is it ok now
find me
Inside every heartbeat
inside every worry
Keep me in your heart again
find me
Inside every heartbeat (over the hills again)
inside every worry
Inside your heart
you ran away
And I would not stay
is it your time
Or is it mine
Find me
inside every heartbeat
Inside every worry
keep me in your heart again
Find me
inside every heartbeat (over the hills again)
Inside every worry
inside your heart