I can see it in your eyes, that you wanna get out
I can see it in your eyes, that you need it right now
That you need it right now
that you wanna get out
Yeah, I just wanna hear the sound
drive our Camaros out of town
Baby, we could leave right now, woah
yeah, I just wanna feel alive
Baby, take your time
smokin' on this loud, woah
Girl, you know you make my cold heart warm with a touch
one kiss, then we f*ckin', I just can't get enough
Put it on me, that's the best part, baby, the trust
trust me, I got nothin' for you other than love
I remember eatin' p*ssy on the back of the bus
I remember gettin' nookie 'til the Sun came up
All the places that you took me, no one came with us
same h*es overlook me, now they on my nuts