Yeah
don't know how she made me feel
But she gave me deja vu
yeah she wear that Saint Laurent
Mix it with the Jimmy Choo
I'm gone give her what she want
Cause she look like Sailor Moon
yeah
Try play me
but the jokes on you
Was born with one
but I'll die with two
Can′t shave me
cause I'll rise and shoot
I'll rise and
no one shows love till it's R.I.P
With this P.Y.T
and she all on me
Been through the trench so it's D.T.B
but I still make love like it's C.L.B
She want love inside this club
I want head inside this coupe
I can′t give her what she want
but she got my song on loop
I can't take one for the team
cause right now all I want is you
Don′t know how she made me feel
but she gave me deja vu
Yeah she wear that Saint Laurent
mix it with the Jimmy Choo
I'm gone give her what she want
cause she look like Sailor Moon
Yeah
in this world of sin
You pick your poison
started off with no one
Brought the boys in
gas no breaks
No time for stalling
I don′t repeat my sh*t
Just give you warning
young Lil n*gga the world is yours
Go make some bread
then flip it again
Never liked school
but I f*ck with Yale
I'll get rich from this
and I'll do it like Ken
I don′t f*ck with groupies
that thrive off motion
But can′t lie bro
she a ten outta ten yeah
New Patek on my wrist
and I'll hit it like Ben
Can′t stop this search
till if find my Zen
Need Mils but more than two
all these girls done been ran through
Born in the slums
from the dirt I grew
Cause she look like Sailor Moon
try play me
But the jokes on you
was born with one
But I'll die with two
can′t shave me
Cause I'll rise and shoot
I′ll rise and
No one shows love till it's R.I.P
with this P.Y.T
And she all on me
been through the trench so it's D.T.B
But I still make love like it′s C.L.B
she want love inside this club
I was head inside this coupe
I can′t give her what she want
But she got my song on loop
I can't take one for the team
Cause right now all I want is you
I couldn′t afford one now it's ten of each ahh
If you′re hearing this I'm outta reach
I can′t invest in these h*es
Cause they try and leach ahh
if you ain't from the slums please don't try and preach on me
Weight of the world
but I′ve got the team on me
Protector Elohim
you can never scheme on me
Never scheme on me
yeah
Never scheme
never scheme
engineered by trmyn