Baby likes it messy
yeah she loves to cause a scene
Touchin’ me in public
like she wants the world to see
All the things you do to me
I don't care if you are using me
I just want to ruin these sheets
oh yeah
I want to kiss you on the mouth
take my tongue and lead it southbound
Baby put some faith in me
put your waist, in my face
Come on violate me
I want you to violate me
Bite my lip, I’m falling for you
you ask, I’m crawling on my knees, at your feet
I can help you with your demons
I want to bring them to life
Don’t keep them buried inside
just want to f*ck you all night, like a p*rn star
Lord forgive me, I've got an appetite
when she looks at me like that
I want to kiss you on the mouth
take my tongue and lead it southbound
Baby put some faith in me
put your waist, in my face
Come on violate me
I want you to violate me
I want to kiss you on the mouth
take my tongue and lead it southbound
Baby put some faith in me
put your waist in my face
Come on violate me
I want you to violate me
I want to kiss you on the mouth
baby put some faith in me
Baby violate me
I want you to violate me