Stop stalking me, I see you 'round the bend again
keep following, see the places you went, yeah
Work your heart again, just a text away from break
stay calm, friend, you will get away f-
Hahaha, let's go
said, b*tch, stop stalking
Walking down a dark path
wish I never traded your love for these racks
I'm gone in the rain, I'm down bad
only call me when you see me going up, so sad (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
Said if you wanting me back then just tell me (just tell me)
back then you wanted to farewell me (farewell me)
Now I'm getting these bags by my lonely
said to come through only if you gon' hold me (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
Stop stalking
walking down a dark path
Wish I never traded your love for these racks
I'm gone in the rain, I'm down bad
Only call me when you see me going up, so sad (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
said if you wanting me back then just tell me (just tell me)
Back then you wanted to farewell me (farewell me)
now I'm getting these bags by my lonely
Said to come through only if you gon' hold me (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
wish you never traded me for him
When you said: It's okay
just forget about it, girl, I'm fine (about it, girl, I'm fine)
Money can't buy happiness for others, to a few, I get paid
that's me, that's me, that's mine (that's mine)
Now I'm making hits, always see you dance
remember back then when I thought that I was always f*ckin' miss
I'm done, holy f*ck, I'm pissed
knew you was a b*tch from the start (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
The first text you sent, like- (ayy, haha)
it's been years, get out my head (out my head)
A lot of time passed remembering the things you said (said, said)
they told me: It's not a big deal, so, instead (yeah, yeah, yeah)
I should be focused on my bands, stackin' all my bread (let's go)
but like, f*ck, where you at? (Where you at?)
You never hit my phone anymore, and that's wack (that's wack)
I'll never find love 'cause I'll let it find me (yeah)
So if you come back, I might see the flag green (b*tch, huh)
now I'm spending big bank rolls, so I can get a feel (get a feel)
The money refill my heart, but it will not heal
rough past with her, so I put up a shield (a shield)
But how she falls around
you in this open field (yeah, yeah, chill, b*tch)
But it's forever and ever
heart's cold, been shot with a thousand Berettas (ah, ah)
Different thoughts in my head
how could I have been better?
But that's past, since start
wish I never had met her (met her)
But I don't know, don't hit my phone (don't hit my phone)
yeah, I like you too much for you to know (yeah)
And once I opened up, it's the days drove off
said once I opened up, it's a day call-off (yeah)
Stop stalking me, stop feeling me (yeah)
stop stalking me (yeah), stop stealin' tees (yeah, yeah)
Yeah, I need my sh*t back for a lovely
days down but I thought she was lovin' me (ayy, ayy)
I remember all them nights
said, b*tch, stop stalking
Walking down a dark path
wish I never traded your love for these racks
I'm gone in the rain, I'm down bad
only call me when you see me going up, so sad (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
Said if you wanting me back then just tell me (just tell me)
back then you wanted to farewell me (farewell me)
Now I'm getting these bags by my lonely
said to come through only if you gon' hold me (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
Stop stalking
walking down a dark path
Wish I never traded your love for these racks
I'm gone in the rain, I'm down bad
Only call me when you see me going up, so sad (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
said if you wanting me back then just tell me (just tell me)
Back then you wanted to farewell me (farewell me)
now I'm getting these bags by my lonely
Said to come through only if you gon' hold me (ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy)
stop stalking me, I see you 'round the bend again
Keep following, see the places you went, yeah
Keep following
see the places you went, yeah