Baby, I'm so fragile
I just need some love
Maybe I'm addicted to the drugs
baby, I'm too fragile
For you to pick me up
maybe I should go, 'cause you don't give a f*ck
I can't really give a f*ck now
'cause the money doin' backflips
My own records got me iced out
and the whip, I got it blacked out
I can't really give a f*ck now
'bout no b*tch or 'bout her best friend
Know they tryna catch me lackin'
tell yo' man's to come and tap in
B*tch, tap in
I got hella h*es tryna get to clappin'
I been movin' too smooth while we talkin'
say she wanna get loose and get lost in—
This sensation
b*tch, tap in
I'ma have to do 'em dirty
b*tch, I'm toxic
I'm a poison in her mind like a toxin
say she really don't mind 'cause she lost in—
My rotation
tap in, shawty give me access
I like me a good girl, I don't do them ratchets, huh
screamin' MOB and that's until my last breath
I was broke last year, it really happened that quick
that one mine, and I keep a few on standby
Can't do more than one at once, I'm on my damn grind
love my brothers, can't be friendly with the other side
Let me take care of the cheque 'cause you can't cover mine
took time, got mine, okay, we on
Like the way you talkin' to me, baby, keep goin'
said I'm not the type of guy that you can leave 'lone
Got a couple more bars, keep the beat on
what's your name, what's your age? I need info
Get your back blown, I'ma break it like a wishbone
move slow, seen 'em fumble out of impulse
Wanna see my DMs?
just be careful what you wish for
I can't really give a f*ck now
'cause the money doin' backflips
My own records got me iced out
and the whip, I got it blacked out
I can't really give a f*ck now
'bout no b*tch or 'bout her best friend
Know they tryna catch me lackin'
tell yo' man's to come and tap in
B*tch, tap in
I got hella h*es tryna get to clappin'
I been movin' too smooth while we talkin'
say she wanna get loose and get lost in—
This sensation
b*tch, tap in
I'ma have to do 'em dirty
b*tch, I'm toxic
I'm a poison in her mind like a toxin
say she really don't mind 'cause she lost in—
My rotation
baby, I'm so fragile
I just need some love
maybe I'm addicted to the drugs
Baby, I'm too fragile
for you to pick me up
Maybe I should go, 'cause you don't give a f*ck